They have one shot to show their spots.
The Cheetah Girls is a family, comedy, drama film directed by Oz Scott.
A four-member teen girl group named the Cheetah Girls go to a Manhattan High School for the Performing
Arts and try to become the first freshmen to win the talent show in the school's history.
During the talent show auditions, they meet a big-time producer named Jackal Johnson, who
tries to make the group into superstars, but the girls run into many problems.
Galleria Garibaldi, played by Raven-Symoné.
Chanel Simmons, played by Adrienne Bailon-Houghton.
Aqua Walker, played by Kiely Williams.
Dorinda Thomas, played by Sabrina Bryan.
Dorothea Garibaldi, played by Lynn Whitfield.
Drinka Champagne, played by Sandra Caldwell.
The Cheetah Girls is a 2003 American musical television film directed by Oz Scott
and based on the book series of the same name by Deborah Gregory.
The Cheetah Girls was the first musical Disney Channel Original Movie.
Upon release, the film was the number one rated basic cable telecast and
premiered to 6.5 million viewers, a record for Disney at the time.
The movie's DVD sold over 800,000 copies.
The film's soundtrack was released on August 12, 2003.
It peaked at number 33 on the Billboard 200 and was
certified double platinum by the RIAA.
Following the success of the film, Disney began developing The
Cheetah Girls as a real-life recording group.
The film explores themes of high school, based on novel or
book, musical, talent show, best friend.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.